罗斯亲了我
Ross kissed me.
天啊…
Oh,my God! Oh,my God! Oh,my God!
很不可思议吧
It was unbelievable!
天啊…
Oh,my God! Oh,my God! Oh,my God!
我们要听全部的经过
Let's hear everything.
莫妮卡，拔掉电话线拿酒来
Monica,get the wine and unplug the phone.
瑞秋，结局好不好？ 我们需不需要面纸？
Rachel,does this end well or do we need to get tissues?
结局非常好
It ended very well.
等我来再讲…
Do not start without me! Do not start without me!
先谈谈那个吻
Okay. All right. Let's hear about the kiss.
是像轻拂过你嘴唇的轻吻呢…
Was it a soft brush against your lips...
还是像… “我现在就要你”的那种吻呢
...or was it a "I gotta have you now" kind of thing?
刚开始很热烈，然后…
Well,at first it was really intense,you know? And then....
天啊，然后我们就完全沉醉了
Oh,God. And then we just sort of sunk into it.
他抱着你吗？ 还是说他的手在你的背上呢？
So was he holding you? Or were his hands on your back?
不，他的手开始时在我腰上
No,actually,first they started out on my waist...
然后往上滑，最后落在我头发上
...and then they slid up and were in my hair.
然后…
And...
…然后我吻了她
...then I kissed her.
舌吻？
Tongue?
对 酷
-Yeah. -Cool.
六人行 第2季 第08集 清单
The One With the List
各位，瞧瞧这个坏小子
All right,check out this bad boy!
12M内存 500M的硬盘…
Twelve megabytes of RAM,500-megabyte hard drive...
里面还有内建试算表的功能…
... built-in spreadsheet capabilities...
再加上传输速度 超过两万八BPS的数据机
...and a modem that transmits at over 28,000 BPS.
你要用它来干嘛？
What will you use it for?
玩游戏之类的
Games and stuff.
根本没有工作 没有适合我的工作
There are no jobs. There are no jobs for me.
等一下，这边有一个
Oh,wait,here's one.
你愿意裸体做菜吗？ 有征裸体厨师的广告？
-Would you be willing to cook naked? -There's an ad for a naked chef?
没有，但你如果愿意裸体做菜 你或许会愿意裸体跳舞
No,but if you'll cook naked,then you might be willing to dance naked.
然后…
And then....
对了，昨晚亲得怎么样了？
So how'd you make out last night?
那真风趣，风趣得很痛苦
That is funny. That is painfully funny.
不，等等…
No,wait,wait.
对，只是痛苦而已
Yeah,that's just painful.
我以为昨天晚上很棒耶
Wait a minute. I thought last night was great.
没错，是很棒 但是当我回到家…
Yeah,it was. But I get home...
我看到茱莉的食盐水 放在我床边的桌上…
...and I see Julie's saline solution on my night table...
我就想“老天啊 我到底在做什么呀？”
...and I think,"My God! What am I doing?"
我跟茱莉这么好的女人 在一起…
Here I am with Julie,this incredible,great woman...
…彼此关怀珍惜…
...who I care about and who cares about me...
而我就那样抛弃一切吗？
...and I'm just throwing all that away?
一瓶食盐水可以讲那么多？
You got all that from saline solution?
我也是这样，给我一瓶维散滴眼露，我就会想：我是谁？
I'm the same way. Show me a bottle of Visine and I'm like, "Who am l?. "
我们现在是在谈瑞秋 你跟瑞秋
Wait. We're talking about Rachel. You and Rachel.
我梦想我跟瑞秋一起 想了十年了
I've been dreaming about me and Rachel for 10 years.
但现在我跟茱莉在一起
But now I'm with Julie.
就好像我跟茱莉，我跟瑞秋
So it's like,me and Julie,me and Rachel.
我跟茱莉，我跟瑞秋…
Me and Julie,me and Rach
瑞秋？瑞秋
Rachel! Rachel.
你 你好吗？
-Hey,you. -How are you?
很好，你呢？
Good. How are you?
很好
Good.
亲爱的 茱莉，你好
-Hi,honey. -Hi,Julie. Hi,Julie?
茱莉…
Julie!
你好吗？
How are you?
很好
Good.
大家都在
So everybody's here.
大家都很好
Everybody's good.
很好并且很棒并且都在这里
Good and great and here.
你不是要弹什么吗，菲比？
Were you gonna play something?
其实我没有… 弹啊
-Well,actually -Play it!
好
All right.
我不知道你戴隐形眼镜 什么？
-Julie,I didn't know you wore lenses. -What?
好，嗨
Okay. Hi.
你们好，嗨，好的
Hello. Hi. Okay.
所以，这是一首关于一个…
This is a song about a love triangle...
…我乱编的三角恋爱故事的歌
... between three people I made up.
叫做“昨晚两人接吻了”
It's called "Two of Them Kissed Last Night."
有个女孩，我们叫她贝蒂
There was a girl We'll call her Betty
有个男孩，咱们叫他尼尔
And a guy Let's call him Neil
我再三强调这一点
Now I can't stress This point too strongly
这故事不是真的
This story isn't real
现在尼尔必须决定 他要放弃哪一个
Now our Neil must decide Who will be the girl that he casts aside
是那个他真心相爱的贝蒂
Will Betty be the one Who he loves truly
还是我们称为露莉的女孩
Or will it be the one Who we'll call Loolie
他必须决定，他必须决定
He must decide He must decide
虽然他纯属虚构，他必须决定
Even though I made him up He must decide
你的资历很不错
Well,this is a nice resume.
不错…
Nice,nice,nice.
可以说非常的可观
Muy impressivo.
很惭愧没一样是真的
Shame none of it's true.
我开玩笑的…
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
全都是真实的，我只是有点紧张，就这样，我现在好点了
No, it's all true. Just a little nervous, that's all. I'm fine now.
这份工作到底是什么呢？ 广告写得很含糊
Mr. Rastatter,what does this job entail? The ad wasn't clear.
麻克力
Macholate.
什么？ 麻克力
-I'm sorry? -Macholate.
一种完全人工的巧克力替代品
It's a synthetic chocolate substitute.
别客气，试一块
Go ahead,try a piece.
对，我们认为 麻克力比巧克力好吃的多了
We think Macholate is even better than chocolate.
好
All right.
我爱这碎碎的感觉
I love how it crumbles.
巧克力不会这样 不会
-You see,chocolate doesn't do that. -No,ma'am.
反正呢，这个应该很快就会通过食品药物管理局检验了
We should be getting our FDA approval any day now.
希望能够赶得上感恩节
Hopefully,in time for Thanksgiving.
照我们看来呢 巧克力已经…
The way we see it,chocolate dominates...
…霸占了大部份跟大餐有关的节日，复活节，圣诞节等
...your major food-preparation holidays. Easter,Christmas,what have you.
我们在想，只要行销搞好了…
But given the right marketing...
…我们能让感恩节 成为麻克力节
...we can make Thanksgiving the Macholate holiday.
哇
Wow.
你不吞下去吗？
Aren't you gonna swallow that?
我只是在等泡泡停止
Just waiting for it to stop bubbling.
是不是很棒？
Isn't that great?
我们…
Well,anyhow...
…在找几个厨师 来搞一些新感恩节食谱
...we're looking for chefs who can create Thanksgiving recipes.
这下你有兴趣吗？
You interested?
绝对…
Abso-...
…有
... -lutely!
我爱创新食谱我爱感恩节 而现在呢…
I love creating recipes,I love Thanksgiving,and now...
…我爱麻克力
... I love Macholate.
真的？
Really?
特别是那种口里的余味…
Especially that aftertaste. I tell you...
…可以缭绕到圣诞节
...that'll last you till Christmas.
麻克力慕斯怎么样？
How about Macholate mousse?
那不是…
It's not...
…感恩节的味道
...very Thanksgiving-y.
那么朝圣者麻克力慕斯呢？
How about Pilgrim Macholate mousse?
哪里像朝圣者啊？
What makes it Pilgrim?
放个皮带扣上去
We'll put buckles on it.
罗斯来电话没？
Did Ross call?
没有，抱歉
No,I'm sorry.
他为什么不打来呢？
Why didn't he call?
他要跟茱莉在一起是不是？
He's gonna stay with Julie.
他要跟她在一起 然后她会一副：
He's gonna stay with her and she'll be:
“我是茱莉，罗斯选我”
"Hi,I'm Julie. Ross picked me.
“我们要结婚，生一堆孩子” “然后全家一起去挖点什么东西”
We'll get married and have lots of kids and dig up stuff together!"
恕我冒犯，她不会这样讲的
No offense,but that sounds nothing like her.
我不知道该怎么办 这简直是一场恶梦
What am I gonna do? This is like a complete nightmare!
我知道，这一定很难受 “不，两个女人都爱我”
I know. This must be so hard. "Oh,no! Two women love me!
她们都那么优秀，我的钱太多，皮包装不下…
They're both gorgeous,my wallet's too small for my 50s...
…我的钻石鞋太紧了
...and my diamond shoes are too tight!"
我有一个办法，罗斯 别碰我的电脑，永远都别碰
-Here's a thought -Don't ever touch the computer.
罗斯，听着 我送你两个字：
Ross,listen. I got two words for you:
三人行（只是一个单词）
Threesome.
你还差一个字没说，如果你想用那个字的话
You still have another word,if you wanna use it.
嘿，我想我知道。帮忙
Oh, hey. I think I know what it is. Help.
我们用理性来分析，好吗？ 我们来列个单子
Let's get logical about this. We'll make a list.
“瑞秋和茱莉，优缺点”
"Rachel and Julie: Pros and Cons."
她俩的名字用不同字型的粗体字
We'll put their names in different fonts...
然后每一栏 可以用不同的颜色来写上
...and I can use different colors for each column.
不能够用笔就好了吗？
Can't we use a pen?
不可以，阿们宗派男孩（17世纪成立）
No,Amish boy.
我们就先从缺点开始 那比较好玩一点
Let's start with the cons because they're more fun.
先列瑞秋
Rachel first.
我不知道
I don't know.
我是说…
I mean....
好吧，我想你可以说她 有时候有一点娇纵
All right,I guess you can say she's a little spoiled sometimes.
可以这么说
You could say that.
有时候…她有点像没头脑
I guess,sometimes she's a little ditzy,you know?
我觉得她有点太注重她的外表
And I've seen her be a little too into her looks.
茱莉跟我有很多共同点…
And Julie and I have a lot in common...
…因为我们都是古生物学家
... because we're both paleontologists,right?
但是瑞秋她只是个女服务生
But Rachel's just a waitress.
女服务生
Waitress.
好了 你们想玩“毁灭战士”（著名的射击游戏）吗？
Got it. You guys want to play Doom?
我们也可以继续
Or we could keep doing this.
还有呢？
What else?
我不知道
I don't know.
她的脚踝有一点胖
Oh! Her ankles are a little chubby.
换茱莉了
Okay,let's do Julie.
她有什么不好的？
What's wrong with her?
她不是瑞秋
She's not Rachel.
这是麻克力饼屑南瓜馅饼
This is pumpkin pie with a Macholate crust.
这个是麻克力红莓蛋糕 而这些是麻克力饼干
This is Macholate cranberry cake,and these are Macholate-chip cookies.
跟印第安人的一样
Just like the lndians served.
天啊
Oh,my God!
“天啊”很好？
"Oh,my God" good?
天啊 我不敢相信你给我吃这个
Oh,my God! I can't believe you let me put this in my mouth.
上帝啊！这一定是恶魔的味道
Sweet Lord! This is what evil must taste like!
我说这个玩意儿不能打印
I tell you,it won't print.
对，那个按钮我按了一百次了
I pressed that button,like,100 times.
就热线而言，你一点都不热情
For a hotline,you're not so hot.
你那边是什么声音？
What is that in the background?
你在看《星际迷航》？
Are you watching Star Trek?
你让茱莉心碎了吗？
So did you break Julie's heart?
是啊，好可怕，她哭，我也哭 她丢东西，打到了我
It was horrible. She cried,I cried. She threw things,they hit me.
我这么做是对的
I did the right thing.
史波克（《星际迷航》中的角色）真的拥抱了他爸爸吗？
So Spock actually hugs his father?
你们有没…
Hey,do you guys have
你去哪儿了？
Where you going?
我刚刚…
I just got back...
…从茱莉那边回来
...from Julie's.
不…
No,no.
不是你想的那样
It's not what you think.
是别的事
It's the other thing.
什么是别的事？
Well,what's the other thing? What do I think?
这个嘛…
Well....
他跟茱莉分手了
He broke up with Julie!
看在老天的份上，去抱抱她呀
Well,go hug her,for God's sakes!
真的？
Really?
真的
Really.
我爱的一直是你
It's always been you,Rach.
天啊
Oh,God.
这真好
Oh,this is good.
这真的很好 我知道…
-This is really good. -I know. I know.
几乎…
It's almost....
我们出去走一走怎么样？ 就我们两个人，没有他们
What do you say we take a walk? Just us. Not them.
好，我去拿外套 好，不…
-Let me get my coat. -Okay. No,hey!
我帮你拿
I'll get your coat.
他去帮我拿外套 他去帮我拿外套，乔伊
He's going to get my coat. He's going to get my coat,Joey!
我真不敢相信
Joey,I can't believe this! This is unbelievable!
那是什么？ 什么？没什么
-What's that? -What? Nothing!
我看到我的名字，是什么？ 不，不，你看…
-I saw my name. What is it? -No,no,see? See?
在印了
It's printing!
那是什么嘛？给我看
Let me see!
有人订了件外套吗？
Hey,someone order a coat?
罗斯，钱德在电脑上 写了关于我的事还不让我看
Chandler wrote something about me and won't let me see.
他有吗？他没有！
He won't? He won't!
因为那是不是…
Because isn't that...
你正在写的短篇故事
...the short story you were writing?
对，那是一篇我正在写的…
Yes,it is a short story...
…短篇故事
...that I was writing.
里面有我？ 那让我看啊
And I'm in it? Let me read it.
不…
No!
好啦 干脆你念给她听好了
-Come on! -Hey,why don't you read it to her?
好吧
All right.
那个时候是夏天
"It was summer.
天气很热
And it was hot.
瑞秋在那里…
Rachel was there.
寂寞的灰沙发
A lonely gray couch.
奈德大叫“看啊”
'Oh,look!' cried Ned.
然后他就是永远的国王了 剧终
And the kingdom was his forever. The end!"
就这样？你只写了这样？ 你是全世界最烂的作家
That's all you wrote? You're the worst writer in the world!
好了，我不再觉得好玩了
This isn't funny anymore.
那张纸上写了关于我的事情 而我想要看一看
There's something about me on that paper,and I want to see it.
不，不可以
No,you don't.
好吧，你们要这么孩子气的话 没关系
All right,fine. If you guys want to be children,that's fine.
我根本就不需要看
I do not need to see it!
这是什么？
What is this?
这是…
That is....
罗斯，这是什么？
What is this?
谢谢 祝你好运
-Thank you. -Good luck.
你只要记得我多为你疯狂
Okay. Just remember how crazy I am about you,okay?
“有点没头脑”？
"Kind of ditzy"?
“太注重外表”？
"Too into her looks"?
“娇纵”？
"Spoiled"?
是有一点娇纵 他应该加上“有一点”才对
A little spoiled. He was supposed to type "little," the idiot!
“只是个女服务生？”
"Just a waitress"?
那是…
Now that was....
我是说，相对于…
I mean,as opposed to....
你念完了没有，瑞秋？
Okay,is this over yet? Rach?
我的脚踝一点都不肥
I do not have chubby ankles!
不，瑞秋…
No! I
好…你看另一边嘛 你看看茱莉那一栏
Okay,look at the other side. Look at Julie's column.
“她不是瑞琪”？
"She's not Rachem"?
瑞琪是什么东西啊
What the hell's a Rachem?
那是什么？因为我是女服务生…
Is that a stupid paleontology word...
而不懂得愚蠢古生物用语吗？
... I wouldn't know,because I'm just a waitress?
不，瑞秋，你不要这样
Rach,come on!
是“她不是瑞秋”
It's "She's not Rachel"!
她不是…
She's not....
我的日记！太聪明了
My diary! Brilliant!
我应该说那是我的日记 她绝对不会逼我念我的日记
If I'd said it was my diary,she wouldn't have made me read it.
那倒是真的，你很适合在紧急事件发生之后成为一个伟人
That's true. You'd be a great person to have around after an emergency.
真不敢相信罗斯列了单子
I cannot believe Ross even made this list.
我知道 简直浑蛋
-I know. -What a dinkus!
放他一马吧 那是钱德的主意
Hey,cut him some slack. It was Chandler's idea.
什么？
What?
很好，我正在希望你提呢
Oh,good. I was hoping that would come up.
这是你的主意？
This was your idea?
拜托，你们想一下 事出必有因
Let's get some perspective here. These things happen for a reason.
对，是你呀
Yeah. You!
菲比，帮我一下，好吗？ 你相信因果报应是狗屁，对吧？
Pheebs,back me up. You believe in that karma crap,don't you?
对，祝你下辈子当粪虫好运
By the way,good luck in your next life as a dung beetle.
瑞秋
Rach!
瑞秋，瑞秋，开门
Hey! Open up! Please?
当别人不开门让你进来的时候 那表示“走开”
When somebody does not buzz you in,Ross,that means,"Go away."
那并不表示请你爬防火梯上来
It doesn't mean,"Climb up the fire escape."
我只是想念一点 你的优点给你听
I just want to read you your "Pro List."
我不感兴趣
Not interested.
第一，你看游戏节目时会哭
"Number one: the way you cry at game shows.
第二，你对朋友的感情很深
Number two: how much you love your friends.
第三，你紧张的时候 玩你头发的样子
Number three: the way you play with your hair when you're nervous.
第四，勇敢地开始你的新生活
Number four: how brave you are for starting your life over.
第五，你很会逗小班
Number five: how great you are with Ben.
第六，还有你的香味
Number six: the way you smell."
罗斯，你在干什么？
What are you doing?
乔伊，帮我开窗，好不好？
You want to open the window?
好呀，来
Oh,yeah.
你在外面干什么？ 我…我…
-What are you doing out there? -I'm....
天啊，你一定冷死了 知道你需要什么吗？
You must be freezing. You know what you need?
来杯热腾腾的麻克力怎么样？
How about a nice,steaming cup of hot Macholate?
瑞秋，开门
Come on,open up.
瑞秋，别这样嘛 你再给我一次机会
Rach,come on. You gotta give me another chance.
不
No.
不？ 我说不
-No? -That's what I said.
也许我们该离开一下
Maybe we should go.
不，你们真的不用走 我们已经谈完了
You don't have to go. We're done.
拜托，我知道你一定…
I know how you must
不，你别说了，罗斯
No! You don't,Ross.
想像一下 你觉得自己最糟的地方
Imagine the worst things you think about yourself.
如果这个世界上 你最信任的人…
How would you feel if the person you trusted most in the world...
不只也这样想
... not only thinks them too...
而且用来当做不跟你在一起的理由，换了你会怎么样？
... but actually uses them as reasons not to be with you.
就算是那样 我还是想要跟你在一起
No,but see,I want to be with you in spite of all those things.
你真是宽宏大量，罗斯
Well,that's mighty big of you.
我说，别走
I said,don't go!
你知道吗？
You know what?
如果今天是你列单子…
If it were the other way around,there is nothing you could put on a list...
…不管你在单子上头写些什么 都阻止不了我跟你在一起
...that would make me not want to be with you.
我猜我们就是那一点不同
Well,then I guess that's the difference between us.
我绝对不会去列单子
See,I'd never make a list.
每一次遇上这种情况 我都不知道要等多久才能开口
I never know how long to wait in this situation before you can talk.
我再等一会儿好了
Maybe a little longer.
我其中的一些食谱用的 麻克力份量或许有点不寻常
In these recipes,the quantities may seem unusual.
像这个椰子麻克力节日干果棒
Like these coconut Macholate holiday nut bars?
我上面写了四杯椰子 四杯碎干果…
I've indicated four cups of coconut and four cups of nuts...
…而只有一大匙的麻克力
...and only one tablespoon of Macholate.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
我们的食品药物管理局执照没有通过
Our FDA approval didn't come through.
实验室老鼠出了问题
Something about laboratory rats.
天啊，真遗撼…
Gosh,I'm sorry.
是呀
Yeah.
好吧，这是给你的支票
Anyhow,here's your check.
还有谢谢你出了这么多力
Thank you for all the trouble you went through.
你做的时候没有吃很多吧？
Listen,you didn't eat a lot of it while you were cooking,did you?
我吃了一些
Well,I ate some.
一些，那还好 一些可以，一些不是很多
Oh,some is fine. Some is not a lot.
那你尿尿的时候 没有灼痛的感觉吧？
So it doesn't burn when you pee,does it?
又是他吗？
Is that him again?
告诉他我很想去接 可是我脚踝太粗走不动
Tell him I'd come to the phone,but my ankles are weighing me down.
我想现在时机不对
I don't think this is the best time.
你帮我一个忙，好不好？
Look,can you do something for me?
当然，什么事？
Sure. What?
好的
All right.
要听音乐吗？
Music?
好吧
Sure.
下一首是 罗斯要点给瑞秋的歌曲
The next one's dedicated to Rachel from Ross.
瑞秋，他要你知道 他为他的行为深感抱歉
Rachel,he wants you to know he's sorry for what he did...
…希望你能从心里原谅他
...and he hopes you can forgive him.
看到你眼若冰霜
See the stones set in your eyes
看到你浑身带刺
See the thorn twist in your side
我会等你的
I'll wait for you
上天实在作弄人
Sleight of hand and twist of fate
她就让我苦苦的等
On a bed of nails she makes me wait
不论你是否在身旁，我会等的
And I'll wait without you
我们刚接到瑞秋的电话 她告诉我们罗斯做了什么
We've just gotten a call from Rachel and she told us what Ross did.
真令人发指 罗斯，如果你在听…
It's pretty appalling. And,Ross,if you're listening...
…我不想再放你点的歌了
...I don't want to play your song anymore.
我们何不将时间 留给还有机会的情侣
Why don't we devote our time to a couple that stands a chance?
艾佛 米雪很抱歉用她的车撞你
Avery,Michelle's sorry she hit you with her car...
她希望你们能够解决问题
...and she hopes you two will work it out.
我有个房间…
There's a room where
…可以去
I can go
倾吐心中的秘密
And tell my secrets to
在我房里
In my room
谢谢你再度光临
Thanks for coming in again.
不客气 我既无道德又需要钱
Not at all. I have no morals,and I need the cash.
咱俩就像照镜子一样
It's like I'm looking in a mirror.
这个东西叫做开心鱼
Anyway,they're called Fish-tachios.
吃起来是跟开心果一样的…
They taste exactly like pistachios...
但主要是用鱼肉重新压制的…
... but they're made of reconstituted fish bits.
来，试试看
Here,try one.
好吧 你没有什么过敏问题吧？
-All right. -You're not allergic to anything?
猫毛
Cat hair.
抱歉
Oh,sorry.